Guide to the Elizabeth L. Eisenstein Papers, 1936-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES XII. PRINTED MATERIALS
  - Interview with Elizabeth Eisenstein, 2010 (Folder 66.9)
  - Jones, Bruce, Chandra Mukerji, 1999 (Folder 66.10)
  - Jouhard, Christian, undated (Folder 66.11)
  - Library of Congress Information Bulletin - on woodcuts in early printed books, 2005 (Folder 66.12)
  - Liddle, Dallas, undated (Folder 66.13)
  - Marotti, Arthur F., undated (Folder 66.14)
  - McGrady, Deborah, 1999; [book review with mention of Elizabeth Eisenstein] (Folder 66.15)
  - New York University Humanities Council Commemorates the Bicentennial of the French Revolution, 1988 (Folder 66.16)
  - Nunberg, Geoffrey, Marshall McLuhan, undated (Folder 66.17)
  - O'Boyle, Lenore, undated (Folder 66.18)
  - Oevres d'Anna Scott, 1999; [exhibition brochure, Musee Archeologique de Nimes] (Folder 66.19)
  - The Pernicious Effects of the Art of Printing, undated (Folder 66.20)
  - Poems on printing - 18th century, undated (Folder 66.21)
  - Poovey, Mary, undated (Folder 66.22)
  - Reisman, David, undated (Folder 66.23)
  - Robert Owen and the Delicious Dream of the Future, 2008; [exhibition catalog, Vassar College] (Folder 66.24)
  - Rose, Jonathan, Dror Wahrman, undated (Folder 66.25)
  - Symposium: What was the History of the Book?, 2007 (Folder 66.26)
  - Tamarkin, Elisa, 2011 (Folder 66.27)
  - Vaughan, Edward, undated (Folder 66.28)
  - Ward, Aileen, circa 1989 (Folder 66.29)
  - Warner, Michael, undated (Folder 66.30)
  - Clippings, undated; [includes letter to the editor by Elizabeth Eisenstein (Washington Post,December 16, 1989)] (Folder 66.31)
  - Clippings, 1968-2013 (Folder 73.1)
  - Clippings, undated (Folders 73.2-3)
  - Miscellaneous articles, circa 2013-circa 2014 (Folder 67.1)
  - Miscellaneous articles, undated (Folder 67.2)
  - Miscellaneous printed materials related to Elizabeth Eisenstein, undated; [book jackets, conference programs, lecture announcements and posters] (Folder 67.3)
- SERIES XIII. MISCELLANEOUS MATERIALS
  - Date books, 1962-2015 (Box 74-75)
  - Photograph - unidentified, undated (Folder 67.4)
  - President's Distinguished Visitor medal - Vassar College, 1988 (Box 76)
  - Unprocessed Materials (Boxes 77-81)
- SERIES XIV. PROFESSIONAL EVALUATIONS
  - (Boxes 67-68)